<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Swift on George Berdovskiy</title>
    <link>https://georgeberdovskiy.com/tags/swift/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Swift on George Berdovskiy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://georgeberdovskiy.com/tags/swift/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PBSOC</title>
      <link>https://georgeberdovskiy.com/projects/mobile/pbsoc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://georgeberdovskiy.com/projects/mobile/pbsoc/</guid>
      <description> Description Description goes here.
Technologies and Languages This application was developed with Swift, uses a storyboard UI, and stores patient data locally with Core Data.
Mobile Screenshots Videos </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vet Anesthesia</title>
      <link>https://georgeberdovskiy.com/projects/mobile/anesthesia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://georgeberdovskiy.com/projects/mobile/anesthesia/</guid>
      <description>Description Veterinary Anesthesia is an iOS application I built in collaboration with the Sacramento County Animal Shelter medical team to help them manage anesthesia protocols for dogs and cats.
First, users input medications using their own dosages and concentrations. Then, they assign them to anesthesia and emergency protocols (in simple terms, lists describing what anesthesia medications should be used during surgery and how much should be administered). This feature offers a great degree of flexibility, allowing countless combinations of drugs depending on the specific needs of veterinarians and technicians.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vet Calculations</title>
      <link>https://georgeberdovskiy.com/projects/mobile/calculations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://georgeberdovskiy.com/projects/mobile/calculations/</guid>
      <description>Description Vet Calculations is an iOS application I built in collaboration with the Sacramento County Animal Shelter medical team to help them perform fluid and blood product calculations quickly and easily.
This application has separate sections for canine and feline records because dosage formulas differ between species. Each section is further divided into pages for fluid, blood transfusion, plasma for albumin deficit, and plasma records.
When creating new records, users enter important information about the animal (such as name, weight, and gender), which is then used by pre-programmed formulas to calculate dosages and rates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Veterinary CRI</title>
      <link>https://georgeberdovskiy.com/projects/mobile/cri/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://georgeberdovskiy.com/projects/mobile/cri/</guid>
      <description>Description Veterinary Anesthesia is an iOS application I built in collaboration with the Sacramento County Animal Shelter medical team to help them manage CRIs (constant rate infusions) for dogs and cats. CRI calculations, which are usually very time-consuming and complicated, become fast and easy to perform with this application!
Veterinary CRI is split into canine and feline sections since dosage formulas differ between the two species. Users can create a new record by entering information about an animal.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
