<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ReactJS on George Berdovskiy</title>
    <link>https://georgeberdovskiy.com/tags/reactjs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ReactJS on George Berdovskiy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://georgeberdovskiy.com/tags/reactjs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Conjugate</title>
      <link>https://georgeberdovskiy.com/projects/web/conjugate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://georgeberdovskiy.com/projects/web/conjugate/</guid>
      <description>Description Conjugate is a free web application that helps students learn Spanish conjugations with short quizzes. Users can either generate random quizzes by selecting the number of verbs and verb endings they wish to study or create their own study sets by manually selecting verbs from our collection (which contains around 500). These tools are a great way to improve conjugation skills or study for Spanish exams!
Quizzes are in the form of a conjugation table that the user needs to fill.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scry</title>
      <link>https://georgeberdovskiy.com/projects/competitions/scry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://georgeberdovskiy.com/projects/competitions/scry/</guid>
      <description>Description For DeveloperWeek 2021, I worked with my friends Shuzheng (Tom) Zhang and Jake Roggenbuck to build Scry, a web application that allows users to quickly view important information about their server (such as open ports, logins, and storage).
Scry includes a local server and client application. The server gathers data about the monitored server, and the client presents that data in an appealing, easy-to-read format. The server runs commands in the background to collect system information and stores it in a MongoDB database.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
